Questions:
- QuestionText: "____ your name?"
  Answers:
  - "Who’s"
  - "What’s"
  - "How’s"
  - "Why’s"
  RightAnswer: "What’s"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "___ old are you?"
  Answers:
  - "Who"
  - "What"
  - "How"
  - "When"
  RightAnswer: "How"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "Выберите верное"
  Answers:
  - "I’m 17 years old"
  - "I’ve 17 years old"
  - "I are 17 years old"
  - "I have 17 years old"
  RightAnswer: "I’m 17 years old"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "Excuse me, ______ speak French?"
  Answers:
  - "do you"
  - "you do"
  - "you"
  RightAnswer: "do you"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "Give it to ___"
  Answers:
  - "i"
  - "he"
  - "me"
  RightAnswer: "me"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "Where _____ from?"
  Answers:
  - "you are"
  - "you"
  - "are you"
  RightAnswer: "are you"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "We have _____ house in Moscow."
  Answers:
  - "any"
  - "a"
  - "an"
  RightAnswer: "a"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "I work in a _________. I am a doctor."
  Answers:
  - "hospital"
  - "hotel"
  - "supermarket"
  RightAnswer: "hospital"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "This is my brother. ___ name is Paul."
  Answers:
  - "Her"
  - "His"
  - "He is"
  RightAnswer: "Her"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "I like apples, but I ______ bananas."
  Answers:
  - "do not like"
  - "like"
  - "do like"
  RightAnswer: "do not like"
  Points: 1
- QuestionText: "I usually go to work ___ train."
  Answers:
  - "on"
  - "with"
  - "by"
  RightAnswer: "by"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "Rosie stayed __ home yesterday afternoon."
  Answers:
  - "in"
  - "at"
  - "to"
  RightAnswer: "at"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "Last night I ____ to the cinema."
  Answers:
  - "went"
  - "did go"
  - "was"
  RightAnswer: "went"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "____ were you at the weekend? I was in Scotland."
  Answers:
  - "When"
  - "Where"
  - "What"
  RightAnswer: "Where"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "I am going to a concert tonight. _____ you like to come?"
  Answers:
  - "Do"
  - "Are"
  - "Would"
  RightAnswer: "Would"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "Excuse me, how do I _____ to the bus station?"
  Answers:
  - "come"
  - "get"
  - "arrive"
  RightAnswer: "get"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "Do you sell stamps? Yes, we do. How _____ do you want?"
  Answers:
  - "any"
  - "many"
  - "much"
  RightAnswer: "much"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "We _____ going to the theatre next Saturday."
  Answers:
  - "will"
  - "do"
  - "are"
  RightAnswer: "are"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "We paid the restaurant bill ____ credit card."
  Answers:
  - "to"
  - "with"
  - "by"
  - "on"
  RightAnswer: "by"
  Points: 2
- QuestionText: "If you ______ money from a friend, you should always pay it back promptly."
  Answers:
  - "borrow"
  - "earn"
  - "spend"
  - "lend"
  RightAnswer: "borrow"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "If the weather _______ bad tomorrow, we can go to a museum."
  Answers:
  - "will be"
  - "was"
  - "is"
  - "would be"
  RightAnswer: "is"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "If I _______ closer to my office, I could walk to work."
  Answers:
  - "lived"
  - "would live"
  - "had live"
  - "live"
  RightAnswer: "lived"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "I’ve got to be at work in five minutes. Don’t worry, I _____ you a lift if you want."
  Answers:
  - "give"
  - "am giving"
  - "'ll give"
  - "'m going to give"
  RightAnswer: "'ll give"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "Julia _____ married since she was 20"
  Answers:
  - "is"
  - "was"
  - "has been"
  - "is being"
  RightAnswer: "has been"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "Don’t worry if I ___ late tonight. I’m going to the gym after work."
  Answers:
  - "am"
  - "will be"
  - "would be"
  - "was"
  RightAnswer: "am"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "I’ve got a terrible headache, and it won’t go away. Have you tried _____ some aspirin?"
  Answers:
  - "to take"
  - "take"
  - "took"
  - "taking"
  RightAnswer: "taking"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "I was wondering _____ I could ask you some questions. Sure, go ahead."
  Answers:
  - "what"
  - "if"
  - "that"
  - "how"
  RightAnswer: "if"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "What clothes should I pack for a trip to Boston? Well, it depends _____ the time of year that you go."
  Answers:
  - "on"
  - "with"
  - "up"
  - "to"
  RightAnswer: "on"
  Points: 3
- QuestionText: "I’ve finished this salad and I’m still hungry. I _____ ordered something more filling."
  Answers:
  - "must"
  - "would have"
  - "should have"
  - "may have"
  RightAnswer: "should have"
  Points: 3